http://www.pacprod.com/cgi-bin/hazelnt.exe?client=84632872&action=serve&menu=left&item=/privacy.htm

Search For:(Advanced Search)
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Pacific Products Gallery has created this privacy statement in order to
demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses our
information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: http://www.pacprod.com.
All pages served in the pacprod.com domain are covered by this privacy policy which was last updated on July 19th, 2008.We use your IP address to help
diagnose problems with our server,
and to administer our Web site.
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.
We use cookies for no other purpose.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services.
We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address)
and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers).
Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers.
The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
We run contests on our site in which we ask users for contact information (like their email address).
We use contact data from our contests to send users promotional material relating to the Pacific Products Gallery.
The contest
winners name and state is posted on our website and in our newsletter.
The users contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings or having their name appear in our newsletter or on our website; see the choice/opt-out section below.
We run a Free Electronic Greeting Card Service on our site in which we ask users for their name, email address and a recipients e-mail address.
This information is used to send the greeting card, and to identify you to the person who is receiving the card.
It may also be used to send
you promotional materials on Pacific Products Gallery products and/or services.
The users contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
We run a Classified Ad Service on our site in which we ask users for contact information (like their email address).
This information is used identify you as the user who placed the classified ad.
It is also used by other users to our site to
contact you regarding your ad.
We do not use this information for any promotional purpose.
The users contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
They may also delete their classified ad by visiting: http://www.pacprod.com/classifieds/delete.htm
We offer a free newsletter on our site in which we ask users for contact information (like their email address).
We use contact data from our newsletter to send users promotional material relating to the Pacific Products Gallery.
The users contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
We offer a guestbook on our site in which we ask users for contact information (like their email address) and other comments.
This
information is displayed on our website for all visitors to see.
We use contact data from our guestbook to send users promotional material relating to the Pacific Products Gallery.
The users contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
We offer a "Joke Of The Day" on our site in which we ask users for their email address if they would like to send jokes to someone else.
this information is only used to send jokes and is not collected or used for any other purpose.
This site uses the services of Valueclick for the serving and/or targeting of
ads, promotions and other marketing messages.
To do this, Valueclick collects
anonymous data about your visit to this and other Web sites, typically
through the use of cookies.
To learn more about Valueclick, go to
http://www.valueclickmedia.com/privacy.shtml (This link will open a new browser window).
This site uses the services of Google Adsense for the serving and/or targeting of
ads, promotions and other marketing messages.
To do this, Google collects
anonymous data about your visit to this and other Web sites, typically
through the use of cookies.
To learn more about Google, go to
http://www.google.com/privacy.html (This link will open a new browser window).
We may use other outside ad companies (in addition to Valueclick and Google Adsense) to display ads on our site.
These ads may contain cookies.
While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies,
and we do not have access to this information.
**Security**
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
All employees of Pacific Products Gallery handle your information with the utmost care and confidentiality and sign a statement to that effect.
None of your personal information is ever stored anywhere where it can be accessed from the Internet.
**Choice/Opt-Out**
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our
partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.This site gives users the following options for
removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can send email to unsubscribe@pacprod.com to be removed from our newsletter mailing list.
You can send email to customerservice@pacprod.com to have your name removed from our guestbook.
You can send email to customerservice@pacprod.com to have your name and advertisement removed from our classified ads. (We will contact you for verification of your identity.)
You can send email to customerservice@pacprod.com to have your registration information removed from auction registration database.
(We will contact you for verification of your identity.)
You can send mail to the following postal address to change or Opt-Out of any of our lists or services (verification of your identity will be required):
3857 Sheldon Drive, Ventura, CA 93003
You can call the following telephone number to change or Opt-Out of any of our lists or services (verification of your identity will be required): (805) 658-7369
**Correct/Update/Review**
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying
information previously provided.
email pacprod@pacprod.comsend mail to the following postal address:
3857 Sheldon Drive, Ventura, CA 93003
call the following telephone number: (805) 658-7369
To better protect the security and integrity of your information,
Pacific Products will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before
changing or granting access to your information.
**Contacting the Web Site**
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,
Copyright © 2020 Pacific Products, Inc. comments@pacprod.com or 805-658-7369
